{
  "extraDescription": "E.g. cube of 2 is represented as \\(2^3\\), and is equal to \\(2 \\times 2 \\times 2\\), i.e. repeated multiplication of 2 up to 3 times, and not \\(2 \\times 3\\)",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(8^3\\)",
      "answer": "512"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^3\\)",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10^3\\)",
      "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1^3\\)",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7^3\\)",
      "answer": "343"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2^3\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5^3\\)",
      "answer": "125"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6^3\\)",
      "answer": "216"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9^3\\)",
      "answer": "729"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3^3\\)",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0^3\\)",
      "answer": "0"
    }
  ]
}
